From virtual assistants and proofreading essays to improvements in healthcare, it seems that artificial intelligence, or AI, is becoming an increasingly larger part of our daily lives and most industries, but would you trust AI to choose your wardrobe?
从虚拟助手、校对论文，到医疗保健的改进，人工智能似乎正成为我们日常生活和大多数行业中越来越重要的一部分，但你会相信人工智能帮你挑选衣橱吗？
There are now numerous apps that create virtual wardrobes, giving users insight into their current fashion style and giving tips to elevate it.
现在有许多应用程序可以创建虚拟衣橱，让用户了解自己当前的时尚风格，并提供提升建议。
One of these apps is Indyx, which describes itself as a 'one-stop digital wardrobe app unlocking the potential of what you already own'.
其中一个应用是Indyx，它自称是"一站式数字衣橱应用，解锁你已有衣物的潜力"。
Indyx encourages you to be environmentally conscious by combining the clothes you already have in your closet, which could mean breaking a cycle of fast fashion, helping you to shop smarter.
Indyx鼓励你通过搭配衣橱里已有的衣服来增强环保意识，这可能意味着打破快时尚的循环，帮助你更明智地购物。
There are similar apps out there too, like Whering, which can create entire outfits for you based on weather or occasion, and StyleDNA, which assesses the colours that suit you best.
还有类似的应用，比如Whering，它可以根据天气或场合为你创建整套服装，以及StyleDNA，它会评估最适合你的颜色。
It's not only consumers using AI, but shops too.
不仅消费者在使用人工智能，商店也在使用。
Clothing retailer M&S started using AI in 2024 to give advice to shoppers on outfit choices based on answers they give in an online quiz.
服装零售商玛莎百货于2024年开始使用人工智能，根据购物者在在线问卷中的回答，为他们提供服装选择建议。
They are asked about their body shape and style preferences, and are then given relevant outfit ideas with the aim being to personalise online interactions.
他们会被问及自己的体型和风格偏好，然后获得相关的服装创意，其目的是实现线上互动的个性化。
Stephen Langford, M&S's director of online, has said the quiz can help choose outfits from 40 million options.
玛莎百货线上业务总监斯蒂芬·兰福德表示，该问卷可以帮助顾客从4000万种选择中挑选服装。
However, there are sceptics within the fashion industry.
然而，时尚行业内部也有人表示质疑。
Michelle Barrett is a personal stylist with Capsule Closet Stylist.
米歇尔·巴雷特是Capsule Closet Stylist的个人造型师。
She warns that consumers must remember that AI doesn't really understand your needs or looks – it's simply creating statistically-plausible looks for you.
她警告说，消费者必须记住，人工智能并不真正理解你的需求或长相——它只是为你创建统计学上看似合理的造型。
She says that when it comes to choosing colours that suit you best, for example, "the apps get different results each time.
她说，例如在选择最适合你的颜色时，"这些应用每次都会得到不同的结果。
The algorithm is placing you into predetermined boxes based on the questions you answer and forms you fill out".
算法根据你回答的问题和填写的表格将你放入预设的框框中。"
So, considering this, will you use AI to help choose your outfits?
那么，考虑到这一点，你会使用人工智能来帮助你挑选服装吗？